I thought my suspicions were wrong.
But it's you!
You fooled me!
I love you so much, Ana.
My love for you has no lies.
I'm not saying what he did was right.
But your husband truly loves you.
Sometimes,
technicalities don't really matter.
Especially if you look at the big picture.
Did he hurt you?
Did he ever hurt you physically?
He didn't, right?
And now that you've dragged me
into all of your lies,
I need to do something to correct them.
Three bodies
have been recovered by the police.
A relative has identified
the body of Brian Robles...
Danny Pascual,
and Joel Geraldo...
We're worried about Beth.
Her siblings and I can't reach her.
Please, Beth.
Eat.
Ben...
Mara!
Beth?
Beth, wait.
Beth!
Beth! Wait!
Beth, let's talk about what happened.
We have nothing to talk about.
No, I know you saw it.
- Beth! Beth, wait!
- I didn't see anything!
I didn't see anything!
Beth!
Uh-um.
Was the woman who died...
your mistress?
No.
She was family.
Was she your relative?
Gingging and I considered her family.
Family? Then why did you kill her?
You must've misunderstood
what you saw, Beth.
It was an accident.
My sister has a mental illness.
She didn't mean to do it.
Beth...
are you going to tell anyone?
Beth?
- Ana?
- Come in.
W-what?
What happened?
Beth...
are you going to tell anyone?
Thank you.
So, what's your plan for me here?
You'll only let me out
when it's time to feed me,
then you'll put me back in the room?
Is that what you do
to people who get in your way?
Are you locked up, Beth?
Are you tied up?
Is there a gag over your mouth?
You can go home...
if you want.
You're free, Beth.
You're free.
But if you don't want to go home yet...
you can use Ana's clothes.
Okay?
Excuse me.
I recognized Brian.
He came to our house.
And the one they couldn't identify
might be Joel.
Who's Joel?
Ben's sister's husband.
Oh, wow. How sordid.
Mom, is that
all you have to say? "How sordid"?
What am I supposed to say?
"Horrendous?" "Gruesome?"
What?
Mom, they're all connected to Ben.
Ben knew them.
I knew the person who died
in the next town last week.
- Does that mean I killed them?
Mom, the police said
the same person may have done this.
And you think it was Ben?
Ana, that's ridiculous!
But Regina said Ben killed her husband.
She's crazy!
And you know what they say.
About what?
About people who believe a crazy person!
- Mom.
- Ana...
Would you rather believe
Ben is a murderer?
What if he really is?
Look...
Ana, you're still in shock, okay?
You should get some rest.
It's not good for the baby
to keep thinking about all these things.
Stop thinking.
So far,
three bodies have been recovered
by the police.
Relatives have identified
the remains of the victims.
Danny Pascual...
Everyone will find out what you're hiding!
A relative identified
the body of Brian Robles.
Ah!
You want me to stop?
Is that what you said?
Well, damn you. "Stop." Exactly.
I've been asking you to do that.
I've asked you to stop.
I didn't want to do this either.
That's why I'm here in Vallente, isn't it?
Simply because I want to live in peace.
The third victim
was identified as Joel Geraldo.
But here you are,
you damn bastard.
You all want to destroy
the things I've worked hard on.
I just want to live a quiet life
with my wife, okay?
You look nice, Beth.
I'll see you, Beth.
So, this is the way
to Uncle Richard's house
from Madam Imelda's place.
Well, it's Ana's house now.
Ben bought it for her.
But does anyone live there?
A caretaker? It doesn't look like it.
Someone lives there.
- Look, there's someone inside.
- Huh?
Maybe Ben hired a caretaker.
Oh, my God.
What the hell?
What's that woman doing there?
She couldn't get inside
if she didn't know the owner, right?
So, there really is something
between them?
Has he moved that woman in?
Are you sure it's them?
Ask Carlos.
But why would he take Beth there?
I don't know.
Maybe he's trying to make you jealous
so you'll take him back.
I don't know.
I don't know what he's doing anymore.
I don't know him anymore.
Hey.
You still haven't talked to each other?
Ana, you know
you can tell me everything, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Here's what we'll do.
I'll send someone to the Bais house...
to find out
if he's really living there
with that physical therapist.
What the hell is that?
It was my house!
And Ben moved that bitch in?
Goodness!
You're being ridiculous, Ana.
He looked for you.
He tried to win you back.
But you wouldn't listen.
Naturally, a man will find
a woman he can lean on.
So, it's your fault
he moved that woman in.
Now it's my fault?
Who's your child here, Mom? Me or him?
Of course you are, my dear.
I'm only thinking about
what's best for you.
Wait a second.
What's really the problem here?
Is it because your husband
is a fake lawyer?
Or is it because of those bodies
that turned up,
even though there's no evidence?
Which is it?
Of all people,
I thought you would understand.
Or has Ben won you over too?
Ma, I need trust.
I need loyalty.
You know,
all I ever hear from you
is "I need this" or "I need that"!
Ana, it's not just about you anymore!
Have you even thought about
the child you're carrying?
Have you?
Mom, I can raise my child
even without a father.
I don't care anymore.
I'm not going back to Ben.
They can play house there for all I care.
Ana, you can't just do nothing.
You need to fix this.
You need to make this right
for your child!
This is what's right.
This is what's right, Mom.
For me and my child.
Regina, you have a visitor.
Regina.
Regina, it's Ana.
Do you remember me?
She's always like this.
She stays quiet
and doesn't talk to anyone.
But is she okay?
Has she been getting sick?
She's okay.
She eats a little.
But she's always quiet.
She just stares outside,
like she's waiting for someone.
Who does she say she's waiting for?
She said she was waiting for her husband.
He promised he'd come back for her.
Nurse, can I take her outside?
Just for a while.
She came here last night.
Ana.
We locked eyes.
But she left right away.
Ben, aren't you wondering
why she came by?
Why didn't she come after me?
Ben...
are you using me?
Did you want Ana to see me here,
so you could make her jealous?
Is that it, Ben?
Last night...
I could've left, Ben. But I didn't!
Ask me why.
Come on, ask me.
Because...
I'm stupid!
God, I'm so stupid!
You have no idea what I've gone through
with you, with Ana, and this damn town!
Ben, I actually hoped...
I had hope
that I could replace Ana in your life.
But I was wrong.
I was wrong for thinking
that I could replace Ana in your life.
I'm sorry, Beth.
Ah...
Mrs. Santos.
Sir, can you please open it?
This is his tattoo.
And...
that's his piercing.
Joel!
My husband!
I told you!
You should've taken me with you!
Now you're gone!
Joel!
My husband...
You should've let me come with you...
Joel...
I told you he was gone.
I told you Ben killed him.
My husband...
Ana, thank you.
You made my wish come true.
What wish?
To find Joel.
You're the only one who has done it.
Not Mara,
not my brother.
Even though it was too late,
what's important is that
I found my husband.
Ma'am, time to take your medicine.
- In just a bit.
- Okay.
Ana, you can have this.
Once I'm out, I'll take it back.
Thank you, Ana.
Focus on recovery, okay?
Take care of yourself.
Be safe.
You should stay safe, Ana.
Your husband is a monster.
Let's go.
- Thank you, nurse.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah, thank you also. Thank you. Okay?
- Thanks.
- Have a nice day.
Attorney Ben Santos.
You need to come with us to the station.
Is Ben already at the station?
Yes, Miss Ana.
Attorney Ben Santos is now
in our custody.
We will take care of
your complaint against him.
Don't hurt him.
Yes, ma'am.
We're just going to talk to him.
Bye.
This is Brian Robles, okay?
I worked with this guy at the firm
a long time ago.
This is Danny.
He is a private investigator...
who was hired by Antonio Saguil
to do a background check on me.
And this guy?
That's Joel.
I don't know his last name,
but he's my sister's partner.
Attorney.
Isn't that too much of a coincidence?
All of these victims are connected to you.
What are you saying?
Do you have anything to do
with all of this, Attorney Santos?
Do you have evidence...
okay?
That connects me to these murders?
Someone saw you.
Someone tipped us off.
A tip?
That tip?
That is not direct evidence.
You should know better than that,
'cause I won't take this sitting down.
Ana?
Gomez, this is not the first time, okay?
That you're trying to see
if I have a motive...
for the murders.
Do you remember
what happened with Antonio Saguil?
You solved that.
It wasn't me who killed him, right?
What could be my motive...
to kill these people?
I've been here for hours.
You do not have a case against me
because you don't have evidence.
So, no evidence...
no case. I go.
Wait, Attorney.
We're not done yet.
You're wasting
your time and your resources
detaining me here.
You have nothing against me.
Or would you like me
to file a case against you?
Thought so.
Beth has been ignoring
my texts and calls, Ana.
I'm worried about her.
Hello, Kat?
Kat, what's the update?
Is Beth still there?
Carlos and I went back to Bais.
She isn't there anymore, Ana.
But I can go back and look again.
No, Kat. Don't do that.
Never go back to that house.
Ana, you're confusing me.
What exactly is going on? Tell me.
Ana!
No answer.
I can't contact her anymore.
Beth is so stubborn.
I told her.
I told her to stay away from you and Ben.
But she didn't listen. She didn't stop.
It's my fault.
Beth might be in danger.
In danger?
Why?
Is Ben going to hurt my friend?
I'll go there! Where is that house?
No, Diane. You can't go there.
I don't know what Ben is thinking.
He might hurt you too.
I won't leave Vallente without my friend!
We don't even know if she's still there.
Kat said she didn't see Beth there.
So, where is she, Ana?
What happened to Beth?
I'll find out. I'm going to go there.
You just told me that Ben is dangerous.
And you want to go alone?
No, I'm coming with you.
Let's call the police.
And what are we going to say?
That Beth might have been kidnapped?
That Beth might be there?
We have no evidence.
What if your husband hurts you?
I know my husband.
If there's one person
who he will never hurt...
it's me.
Ben?
Beth.
Ana.
You came.
Thank you.
I knew you'd come.
What did you do?
Oh. Ah, this?
I chopped some chicken.
I mean...
Funny, 'cause I was thinking you'd come.
So I'm trying to cook.
Ana.
I-I'll clean up.
Sorry, Ana.
I didn't know
you'd gotten the house cleaned up.
Yes. Yes, Ana.
I also had our room cleaned.
I cleaned it up for us.
Of course, our baby.
How are you, Ana?
I miss you.
Did you go to the doctor? How's our baby?
Is this the baby's room?
Yeah.
It's not finished yet.
- It's okay.
- No, Ana.
It's supposed to be a surprise.
I still have some work to do inside.
- I just wanna see.
- Ana.
Ana...
It's messy here.
There's paint everywhere.
I'm painting this.
I told you it's not ready.
You like it?
Yeah.
- You wanna pick a color?
- It's nice.
Is this Beth's?
Yes.
Why is there blood?
Ben.
What did you do?
She's gone, Ana.
What? Beth is gone?
Oh, my God, Ben!
What did you do?
Ana, she left.
I don't believe you.
That's the truth.
Ben, what did you do to Beth?
Where is she?
- Is she still here?
- Ana.
Is she still here?
- Where did you hide Beth?
- Ana, she already left.
Beth! Beth!
Beth!
Beth?
- Beth!
- Ana!
- Where is she?
- Ana, she's not here anymore!
She's gone because you killed her?
You killed her, Ben,
just like you killed Joel.
Oh, my God.
Did you think I was so stupid...
to not see the connection
of the three people you killed?
Ben, I know!
I know you killed them
because they found out
the secrets you were hiding!
You've been fooling everyone.
You've been using the cops
and bending the law to your advantage.
How could you do it?
You can manipulate everything, but not me!
Not me. Not anymore. I'm done.
What do you mean?
I thought you came here...
I thought you came here
because we're gonna fix things.
No.
There's nothing left to fix.
We're done, Ben.
One day,
you'll pay for what you did,
but you won't drag me and my son
into this.
I won't let you do it.
Wait, Ana...
Don't do this.
No...
- No...
- Stop.
Please, let go. Please.
Please, you can't leave me.
Ben!
I can, and I will.
No!
Wake up!
Mama!
You really are smart.
But I'm not like you.
Then you just have to study hard.
Do you agree?
Fighting back, huh?
Fight back now!
That's not the kind of life
I want for our child.
You know how my life was before, Ben.
We will be different.
We will be better as parents.
No!
Ben!
Ben?
No, no.
No, no, no...
No...
No!
No... Ana!
Beth? Beth...
Betchay?
Beth?
Beth, it's Diane.
Ana!
- Open up--
- Ana!
No! Stay away from me!
Who are you calling?
Ana, stop!
- Stop! Don't come closer!
- Stop!
This is Beth's phone.
Who are you calling?
- No, Ben! Please!
- Who are you calling? Huh?
- Give me your phone. Don't call anyone!
- Stop...
Please, talk to me!
Talk-- Ana!
- Don't come any closer!
- Stop!
- No! Let me go!
Let me go!
- Ana?
- Stop!
Ana. Ana...
Ana! Stop!
Ben...
Hello? Officer?
Ben! Ben!
Ben, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Ben...
I'm sorry, Ben.
Ana...
There's... a snake.
Oh, my God...
Oh, my God. Ben, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were...
- I--
- Shh.
I didn't know.
Oh, my God, Ben.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, Ana.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
I lied.
I lied so many times.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
I lied because...
I was so afraid to lose you.
Every day,
I fought for...
- ...our lives and our dreams.
- No, no, no, no...
Out of all the lies I told,
only one thing...
remains true.
I love you so much.
Please take care of our baby...
Ben?
Ben. Ben?
Ben...
No...
Move!
- They're inside!
- Men, move!
Ana?
Men, search the whole house!
Please find my friend, Beth, too.
Beth?
Ana?
No one survives pain unchanged.
When you get hurt,
you change in a lot of ways.
There are some things
that never go back
to what they used to be.
Things that...
you choose not to be
part of your life anymore.
When you've gone through the most painful,
the most difficult moment in your life,
you have no choice but to face it.
Sometimes, you do it
for the ones you love,
but it should also be for yourself.
Thanks for the treat.
No, thank you
for taking care of my siblings.
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm always glad to help out.
What's that?
Oh, this?
I'm planning to give it away.
I won't get to use it anyway.
To help you forget about them?
I guess so.
You've had a tough time in Vallente.
Especially with what Ben did to you.
What exactly happened?
I don't know.
I was out of my mind back there.
What's important is it's all over.
You've moved on.
And finally,
you've opened up your own clinic.
Yes, finally!
I'm glad you found a business partner too.
I hope I get to know them.
Oh, yeah, they're almost here.
Oh!
Hi, Beth. Sorry I'm late.
- Traffic was so bad.
- It's okay. This is Diane.
- My friend.
- Hi, Diane.
I'm Attorney De Castro.
Hello, Attorney.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
So, um...
when do we start?
Pain changes how you see things.
Juancho?
Auntie!
Son!
Hi, Ma!
It shows...
what's really important.
And what you can survive
in the name of love.
That's my experience
as a designer, a daughter,
a wife,
and as a person.
Dear residents of Vallente,
our Child of Visayas 2031,
Ana Madrigal-Santos!
And presenting the award
is our very own...
Mayor Benjamin Santos!
- Thank you, son.
- You're welcome.
Thank you.
I am so proud of you, stranger.
Smile.
The opening of the new law firm...
- ...coincides with the news of the opening
of his new business venture,
a physical therapy clinic.
More details soon.
Hello?
Hello, Ma'am Ana.
- Yes?
- We have a new client
requesting a gown for the opening
of her physical therapy clinic.
She insists that you accommodate her.
And she is...
Elizabeth Valdez.
Papa?
Elijah?
Mama!
Oh...
Baby.
What happened, dear?
Why are you up at this hour?
I had a dream that Papa went outside.
- Mama!
- Oh! Oh...
Mm. Baby.
I'm scared, Mama.
It's okay.
He'll be back.
As the mother of La Familia,
I make sure
that whenever we make a decision,
we always put the company first,
especially our safety standards.
I am La Familia.
- I won't let you ruin this company.
That's cruel!
That's why your family left!
Karma will catch up to you!
That's just karma. I am Diana Aragon.
Miss D, something went wrong
at the feeding program.
Does anybody know what caused this?
Give me answers!
- Miss D! Miss D!
- Miss D!
I just know that someday,
you'll be the main star.
It's your birthday.
It's okay, Ma.
You know
I don't like celebrating anyway, right?
What's wrong?
Your dad ran off with all our money.
- How much was it?
- About a million.
According to our sources,
Ms. Aragon has an only daughter.
She's so lucky then!
Must be the heir to the fortune.
What they need to see is authenticity.
And trust me,
your family is very, very marketable.
The first day
of the only daughter at La Familia.
- Good morning, Miss D.
- Miss D?
Your family
is still the only one you can trust.
Where is this family now as we talk?
I choose my daughter.
And I chose to understand her too.
Saving Diana means saving La Familia.
What are we supposed to do about all this?
She's not looking for a real daughter.
A doll. A doll she can dress up
and make do whatever she wants.
You ruined our relationship.
Patricia is like this
because you always made her feel
like she was never enough.
You're surrounded by beautiful things,
but we all know you're all alone.
- Enough!
- Stop!
I thought something changed,
but nothing has.
You just have to give her a chance.
- She's not a bad person.
- Only to you.
What kind of daughter are you?
Before asking me
what kind of daughter I am,
ask yourself what kind of mother she is.
Is that really how you see me?
All I know is...
you'd do anything
and sacrifice everything for La Familia.
I'm facing you as a human,
so show me some respect.
Then stop acting like this is
the biggest inconvenience of your life.
Hey!